<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Antoine Kassi</title>
    <link>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Antoine Kassi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Algorithmic Trading</title>
      <link>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Algorithmic trading is a method of executing orders using automated pre-programmed trading instructions accounting for variables such as time, price, and volume. This type of trading attempts to leverage the speed and computational resources of computers relative to human traders.
Algorithmic Trading The majority of traders lose money. They lose money not because they don&amp;rsquo;t understand the market, but simply because their trading decisions are not based on solid research and proven trading methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projets 3: Portfolio Optimization</title>
      <link>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Modern Portfolio Theory It was formulated in the 1950 by Harry Markowitz.
what is the main idea? A single stock is quite unpredictable or risky: we do not know for certain whether a stock will go up or down.
 But we may combine several stocks, in order to reduce risk as much as possible. DIVERSIFICATION.
when a given value of stock goes down another goes up. Combining assets is the main idea: it is the same as the black-scholes Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Data scientist motivated and passionate about financial markets and algorithmic trading, I want to work as a Data Scientist. My goal is to be one of the best data scientist and trader, using my programming skills to crack the financial markets. I am passionate about self-learning, all my skills in programming and in the financial markets, I acquired them through books, training, tutorials and research.
Skills area:
 Data Analysis Data science Portfolio Analysis Financial Markets Risk Management Quantitative Analysis Algorithmic Trading  I am currently looking for an internship in one of these fields above to progress in my career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonio2505.github.io/antoine_kassi/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     Gmail: knogbou@gmail.com   LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/antoine-kassi-09003a123/   GitHub: https://github.com/antonio2505   WhatsApp: https://wa.me/+22569908862    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
